learn how to style your hair in a cool way for Onam?  So,
this hairstyle is for those who want a side-parted hairstyle this Onam
.  Take the same calculation for the side
partition.  Let's take a small section of hair, pull it
back a little, and then add some hair from the front to it, one by one, into
each
braid
.  A small braid is made,
then some hair from the front is
taken and sectioned off.  So
we can tie it off with one side complete
.
Let's try this hairstyle not only on the side but also with a center partition
.  Let's tie one side and
try the upper side in the same way
.  Then you can try an open hairstyle with this
or a bun hairstyle or
two days ago we
posted a video of Aayur Minjal.  So
you can try.  So
anyway, try it this Onam
.  So after two days
together, it's a lion.  Bye.